Hmm, listen to that fire crackling, my
dear.
Nights like this always take me back.
Back to a time long before you were born.
A time when life moved softer and the
world felt
quieter.
Yes, the 1960s.
When I was a young boy, life was simple
but full
of magic. No screens, no
buzzing phones. Just the open sky and a
heart that believed
anything could happen.
I remember summer evenings like this. My
friends and I racing
bicycles down dusty roads, chasing the
wind. The sunset glowing
warm gold and red, like this fire on your
cheeks.
And at night, we'd sit around a little
fire, just like we are now.
The grown-ups whispered about the world
changing,
music louder, dreams bigger, hope
growing in new ways.
I still remember hearing, let it be, on a
neighbor's radio.
Even now, it feels like warm bread to my
soul.
Comforting, familiar, safe.
Back then, my biggest worry was if my kite
would fly tomorrow.
And my greatest treasure was a tin box of
pebbles, little notes,
and one silver button from the market.
Funny how small things felt huge. But the
memories closest to my heart are nights
like this.
When my own grandfather sat with me by a
fire.
Telling stories of his youth as sparks
drifted into the dark sky.
So tonight, my dear, as this fire crackles
softly
and the night wraps around us like a
blanket.
I want you to remember this moment, its
warmth,
its quiet.
My voice sharing a piece of the 1960s.
Because someday, years from now, you might
sit by your
own fire with a little one.
Telling them about a quiet evening back in
the 2020s,
when your old grandpa shared his heart.
Now close your eyes, sweetheart.
Let the fires whisper and grandpa's
memories carry
you to sleep.
Good night.
Good night, my dear.